[{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980231134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":22487,"timeElapsed":61419},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980238632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":7497,"timeElapsed":68917},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980249025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":10391,"timeElapsed":79310},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980252989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":83274},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6057,"timeElapsed":89332},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8449,"timeElapsed":97782},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980276003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8506,"timeElapsed":106288},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980282461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":6457,"timeElapsed":112746},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8450,"timeElapsed":121196},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980300198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8059,"timeElapsed":130483},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":137003},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2523,"timeElapsed":139527},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2627,"timeElapsed":142155},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3347,"timeElapsed":145503},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5157,"timeElapsed":150661},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4557,"timeElapsed":155219},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5615,"timeElapsed":160835},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":165522},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4861,"timeElapsed":171297},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3356,"timeElapsed":174654},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2379,"timeElapsed":177034},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2499,"timeElapsed":179534},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4941,"timeElapsed":184476},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980358494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4301,"timeElapsed":188778},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4901,"timeElapsed":193680},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3861,"timeElapsed":197542},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2740,"timeElapsed":200283},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":26184,"timeElapsed":227437},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6879,"timeElapsed":234317},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6207,"timeElapsed":240526},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3316,"timeElapsed":243842},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4469,"timeElapsed":248311},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5976,"timeElapsed":254288},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2555,"timeElapsed":256844},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":8739,"timeElapsed":265584},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2923,"timeElapsed":268508},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11794,"timeElapsed":285939},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5077,"timeElapsed":291017},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2740,"timeElapsed":293757},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4341,"timeElapsed":298099},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2738,"timeElapsed":300837},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4397,"timeElapsed":305235},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3078,"timeElapsed":308314},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4782,"timeElapsed":313096},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2088,"timeElapsed":315185},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":12362,"timeElapsed":328518},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4528,"timeElapsed":333046},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9025,"timeElapsed":342072},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2115,"timeElapsed":344188},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3043,"timeElapsed":347232},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":350477},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3307,"timeElapsed":353785},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3997,"timeElapsed":357783},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531382,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3883,"timeElapsed":361667},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5897,"timeElapsed":367565},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":18000,"timeElapsed":386462},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2393,"timeElapsed":388855},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2868,"timeElapsed":391724},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":393992},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566085,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2377,"timeElapsed":396370},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2843,"timeElapsed":399214},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2387,"timeElapsed":401602},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":405198},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2860,"timeElapsed":408058},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":411190},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5743,"timeElapsed":417840},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4549,"timeElapsed":422390},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1858,"timeElapsed":424249},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2667,"timeElapsed":426917},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3788,"timeElapsed":430705},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":434245},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4217,"timeElapsed":438463},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":440883},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2611,"timeElapsed":443495},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":12808,"timeElapsed":457119},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6439,"timeElapsed":463559},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1817,"timeElapsed":465377},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2251,"timeElapsed":467629},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4028,"timeElapsed":471658},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3379,"timeElapsed":475038},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3509,"timeElapsed":478548},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5703,"timeElapsed":484252},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2281,"timeElapsed":486534},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5639,"timeElapsed":493088},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4013,"timeElapsed":497102},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2362,"timeElapsed":499465},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1961,"timeElapsed":501426},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3397,"timeElapsed":504825},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2241,"timeElapsed":507067},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":510641},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3172,"timeElapsed":513813},{"subjectID":"3ttx0vh9he","prolificID":"66af7c90e296b0495a6af492","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2450983520328206edc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2387,"timeElapsed":516201}]